<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on</title><link>/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bash getopts</title><link>/post/2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/2/</guid><description>Bash builtin. Short options only
usage() { echo &amp;#34;Usage: $0 [-s &amp;lt;45|90&amp;gt;] [-p &amp;lt;string&amp;gt;]&amp;#34; 1&amp;gt;&amp;amp;2; exit 0; } while getopts &amp;#34;:s:p:&amp;#34; o; do case &amp;#34;${o}&amp;#34; in s) s=${OPTARG} ((s == 45 || s == 90)) || usage ;; p) p=${OPTARG} ;; *) usage ;; esac done shift $((OPTIND-1)) if [ -z &amp;#34;${s}&amp;#34; ] || [ -z &amp;#34;${p}&amp;#34; ]; then usage fi echo &amp;#34;s = ${s}&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;p = ${p}&amp;#34; Usage $ .</description></item><item><title>How to set boundaries with your todo list</title><link>/post/4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/4/</guid><description>I started dividing my to-do list into 1) things I have to do, 2) things I want to do, and 3) things other people want me to do. Life changing! I often don’t get to 3 and I finally realized omg, is this what it means to have boundaries?!1
Does this just translate to my [[4.2 Todoist]] P1-P4 prioritisation system?
Links [[4.1 The PARA Method]] Medium Article&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>The PARA Method</title><link>/post/4.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/4.1/</guid><description>General thoughts How does PARA map to my Johnny Decimal index? This PARA approach links PKM systems to execution and productivity tools. The PARA methods are listed in order of actionability; i.e. active projects first, areas of responsibility second, resources third and archives fourth.
Method Description (P)rojects A series of tasks linked to a goal, with a deadline. Review each day
Has a goal to be achieved Has a deadline Fits more with todo management techniques Can fall under multiple Areas of Responsibility Getting a sense of current projects is the only way to assess capacity/utilisation.</description></item><item><title>Todoist</title><link>/post/4.2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/4.2/</guid><description>My preferred task management platform Has a web interface iOS app Good UI/UX Uses natural language input Has an open and accessible API Links [[4 How to set boundaries with your to-do list]]</description></item><item><title>What Zettelkasten Actually Is</title><link>/post/1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/1/</guid><description>The ability of software tools to do hyperlinking seems to have seriously muddled the basic concept of Zettelkasten. Although it might be that this was never particularly unified, and I just think of Luhman’s system as the “true Zettelkasten”.
Many discussions seem to suggest that Zettelkasten is merely the use of sequential ID numbers for note identification, rather than using note titles etc. My preference is for the use of the Luhman-style expanding tree ID’s - i.</description></item></channel></rss>